Alexander, Gabriel Additional Arbitration Files 5789
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Gabriel Alexander Additional Arbitration Files
1932-1985
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Alexander, Gabriel
5789
10 cubic feet
10 linear ft.
Records (documents), collective labor agreements.
Collective labor agreements
3124689
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 06, 2012
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5120: Southern Bell Telephone and Telegraph Company and the Communications Workers of America Arbitration Files 5133: Gabriel Alexander Arbitration Files 5602: Gabriel Alexander Additional Arbitration Files 5678: Gabriel Alexander Additional Arbitration Files 6150 mf: Robert J. Alexander Papers Interview Collection on Microfilm
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States -- Sources.; Hastings Manufacturing Company; International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Local 337; International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Local 138; Jones and Laughlin Steel Corporation; Kelsey-Hayes Company; Midwest Machinery Movers, Inc.; Midwest Steel Division National Steel Corporation
3124689
- AA Gage Division of U. S. Industries, Inc. and UAW, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Discipline: Rule for Absence before or after Holiday.. Date closed: 3-31-78
- General Motors Corporation Chevrolet Division and UPGWA, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Discipline: Failure to Properly Perform Duties.. Date closed: 5-10-78
- General Motors Corporation Inland Division and URWA, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Discipline: Absenteeism, Last Chance Agreement.. Date closed: 2-13-78
- General Motors Corporation Inland Div. and URC etc. Workers, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Discharge. Date closed: 2-13-78
- Jones and Laughlin Steel Corp. and USWA, Local 1843, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Wages: Incentives: Requested Change Under Section IX-C-2. Date closed: 1-12-79
- Jones and Laughlin Steel Corp. and USWA, Local 1843, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Wages: Incentives; "Related" Indirect Jobs.. Date closed: 10-17-78
- Jones and Laughlin Steel Corp. and USWA Local 1272, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Incentives: Earliest Practicable Date for Installation.. Date closed: 9-11-78
- Jones & Laughlin Steel Corp. and USWA Local 1211, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Wages: Classification; Revisions in Established Job of Eddy Current Inspector.. Date closed: 1-5-79
- Marquette Cement Manufacturing Company and UCL&GW, AFL-CIO, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Subcontracting: Production of Stone.. Date closed: 8-31-79
- Pauly Cheese Company, Division Swift and Company and IBT, Local 75, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Discharge. Date closed: 10-27-76
- Port Authority of Allegheny County and ATU, Div. 85, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Pay for Day Not Worked.. Date closed: 5-15-79
- Swift and Company, Albuquerque Sales Unit and AMC&BWA, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Discipline: Failure to Report Motor Vehicle Accident.. Date closed: 9- 16-77
- Dollar Electric Company and UAW Local 155, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Discharge. Date closed: 10-23-74
- East Ohio Gas Company and Natural Gas Workers Union, Local 555, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Discipline: Demotion; Multiple Penalties.. Date closed: 7-1-74
- Electric Apparatus Company and UAW Local 568, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Wages: Classification; Maintenance Painting.. Date closed: 4-16-75
- Diamond International Corp. and Diamond Gardner Employes, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Grievance Procedure,: Timeliness. Date closed: 6-26-73
- Melling Forging Company and UAW Local 724, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Discharge: Violation of Parking Lot Rules; Corrective Discipline. Date closed: 8-4-73
- Melling Forging Company and UAW Local 7 24, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Discipline: Discharge or Quit.. Date closed: 8-14-73
- Mennel Milling Company and A rival Federation Of Grain Mixers, AFL-CIO, Local 58, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Seniority: Shift Preference; Definition of Classification and Vacancy.. Date closed: 4-9-74
- Metropolitan Insurance Company and Insurance Workers Int'l Union, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Arbitrability of Grievances.. Date closed: 11-1-74
- Michigan Screw Products Inc. and UAW Local 189, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Discipline: Drinking Liquor on Premises.. Date closed: 4-3-74
- Midwest Steel Division National Steel Corporation and USWA, Local 6103, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Wages: Incentives; Defective Product from Temper Mill.. Date closed: 10-5-73
- Midwest Steel Division National Steel Corporation and USWA, AFL-CIO Local 6103, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  Arbitration: Remedy for Failure to Notify of Schedule Change.. Date closed: 10-16-73
- Midwest Steel Division of National Steel Corporation and USWA, AFL-CIO, Local 6103, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  Contracting Out: Trash Removal.. Date closed: 10-26- 73
- Green River Still Corporation and USWA, AFL-CIO, Local 4959, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Wages: Incentives; New Plan; Equitable Earnings Opportunity.. Date closed: 2- 5-74
- Griffith-Hope Company and USWA, Local 1677, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Shortened Work Day: Notice of Layoff; Call in Pay.. Date closed: 12-12-73
- Harnischfeger Corporation and USWA, AFL-CIO, Local 1114, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Job Evaluation: Operator-Gear Shaper and Gear Grinder.. Date closed: 9-6- 73
- The Journal Company and Milwaukee Web Pressmen, Union #23, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Plating Up Grievance (Settled at Recess). Date closed: 2-1-74
- Kelsey-Hayes Company and UAW Local 985, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Wages: Classification; Set-ip or Leader.. Date closed: 6-3-74
- Kelsey-Hayes Company (Milford Plant) and UAW, Local 985, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Discipline: Oral Agreement Regarding Absence.. Date closed: 6-4-74
- Babcock and Wilcox, Int'l Brotherhood of Boilermakers Local 900, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Discipline: Theft of Company Property.. Date closed: 12-7-81
- Borg-Warner Corporation UAW, Local 803, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Seniority: Demotion for Incompetence. Discipline: Demotion for Unsatisfactory Work.. Date closed: 12-22-81
- Don Lee Distributor Inc. and IBT, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Discipline: Theft.. Date closed: 9-23-81
- Edgecomb Metals Company and IBT, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Reporting Allowance, Right to go Home. Date closed: 4-7-81
- Fisher Controls Company, Inc. & Unit One, Amalgamated Local, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Subcontracting: Janitorial Work. Date closed: 3-16-81
- Ford Motor Company and Local 135, Industrial Fire Fighters Association, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Seniority and Ability: Shift Preference Transfers.. Date closed: 3-31- 81
- Grand Rapids City Coach Lines c. and Local 8 36, ATU, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Discipline: Mishandling Passenger Fares.. Date closed: 3-25-81
- Hanna Furnace Corporation and USWA, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Seniority and Scheduling.. Date closed: 11-25-81
- Hastings Manufacturing Co. and UAW, Local 138, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Fringe Benefits: Insurance Eligibility on Return from Layoff.. Date closed: 12-9-81
- Ideal Industries, Inc. and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Dist. 123, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Wages: Incentives; Changed Incentive Plan.. Date closed: 6-16-81
- Lutz News Company and Newspaper Drivers and Handlers Local 372, IBT, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Christmas Bonus Grievance. Date closed: 9-9-81
- Rock Island County Metropolitan Mass Transit Dist. and Division 313, ATU, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  New Contract Terms.. Date closed: 11-20-81
- National Broach & Machine and USWA, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Discipline: Absenteeism. Date closed: 1-19-81
- Pepsi Cola Bottling Co. and Local 337, IBT, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Discipline: Tardiness; False Time Clock Card.. Date closed: 2-5-81
- Reynolds Metals Company and International Union UPGWA, Local 32 8, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Discharge: Leaving Plant Without Ringing out; Falsification of Guard Report.. Date closed: 8-27-81
- Square D Company (Middletown Manufacturing Plant) and IBEW, AFL-CIO Local 2258, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Guaranteed Hours; Time Lost for Medical Reasons.. Date closed: 6-2-81 '"-
- City of Sterling Heights, Michigan and Sterling Hgts. Fire Fighters Assn. ', 1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Discipline; Of f Duty 'Misconduct; Shoplifting; Evidence. Date closed: 1-15-81
- City of Sylvan Lake and Fraternal Order of Police, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Discipline: Discharge for Violating Rules and Instructions.. Date closed: 6-3-81
- Veterans Administration Hosp. and Local 2280, American Fed. Government Employees, AFL-CIC, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  FMCS File No. 804/20067. Date closed: 1-6- 81
- Western Reserve Telephone Company and IBEW, Local 1507, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Discipline: Attendance Program. Date closed: 11-25-81
- Westinghouse Electric Corp. and Federation of Westinghouse Independent Salaried Unions, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Termination of E. Yonika. Date closed: 8-20-81
- The Bendix Corporation & UAW, AFL-CIO, Local 46, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Grievance No. 462, Scheduling Overtime During Periods of Layoff. Date closed: 5- 4-82
- Columbus & Southern Ohio Electric Company & IBT Local 1466, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Case No. 52 30 0358 81 Discrimination: Apprentices & Journeymen. Date closed: 5-7-82
- The Dearborn Inn and Local 1064, United Catering etc., 1982 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Michael Carnahan Grievance. Date closed: 3-26-82
- Faygo Beverages & IBT Local 337, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  FMCS 82K/17930. Date closed: Settled at Hearing
- Genesee County Drain Commissioner and AFSCME, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  t FMCS't 81K/17880 ' Case No. 12992. Date closed: 6-4-82
- Genesee County Prosecutor and Gen. Co. Government Bar Assn., 1982 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Paul Murray Grievance FMCS Case No. 82K/27461. Date closed: 11-29- 82
- Granite City Steel and USWA, Local Union No. 30, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Gr. 309-79-7 - Work Assignment; Local Working Conditions.. Date closed: 3-15-82
- Granite City Steel and USWA, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Gr. Nos. 484-81-9; 485-81-9 and 309-79-7. Date closed: 3-15-82
- Johns-Manville Sales Corp. and Glass Bottle Blowers Assn., 1982 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Gr. # G-28-51-81-55 - Sub-contracting: Painting. Date closed: 6-8-82
- Morgan Engineering Company and UAW, AFL-CIO, Local 2254, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Case No. 53-30-0176-81 - Discipline: Theft, Possession of Intoxicants and Fireworks. Date closed: 6-15-82
- Nabisco Inc. and IBT, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Alvin Bauman Grievance - Discharge; Petty Theft, Mental Illness. Date closed: 3-19-82
- Signal Delivery Service Inc. and IBT, Local No. 24 9, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Case No. 55-30-0031-82 Discharge: Major Chargeable Accident. Date closed: 12-13- 32
- Dundee Cement Company and United Cement, Lime etc., 1983 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Seniority: Transfers during Curtailed Production Periods. Date closed: 5-19-83
- Grand Rapids Die Casting Corporation and UAW Local 159, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Fringe Benefits: Dental and Prescription Drug Ins; Extent of Employers Liability for Premiums. Date closed: 9-28-83
- Harlo Corporation and IBEW Local 107, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Fringes: Insurance; Hospital/ Medical/Surgical, Premium Charges. Date closed: 10-12-83
- H. J- Heinz Company and RWDSU, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  (Case settled after hearing). Date closed:
- ITT Hancock Industries, Inc. and UAW, Local 670, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Discipline: Absenteeism. Date closed: 11-3-80
- Lake Shore, Inc. and USWA, Local 3111, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Seniority and Ability: Promotions; Posted Vacancy; Welder.. Date closed: 4-27-83
- Warner-Lambert Company Parke-Davis Division and OCAW, Local 7-176, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Termination: Absences Due to Illness.. Date closed: 12-29-83
- The Seven Up Bottling Company of Detroit and IBT, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Discipline: Unsatisfactory Work.. Date closed: 4-2-82
- Swift and Company and General Teamsters Union, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Discharge: -Refusal to Work. Date closed: 6-15-83
- Alma Plastics Co. and OCAW Inter'1 Union, Local 7-540, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Temporary Transfers for Lunch Period Relief.. Date closed: 1-6-83
- American Broadcasting Co. and Directors Guild of America, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  (Partially heard and cancelled). Date closed: 11-16-83
- Ames Company - Division of McDonough and USWA Local 1651, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Seniority: Reduction in Force: Bumping to Essential Job.. Date closed: 11-10- 82
- Deneau vs American Broadcasting Company, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  \. Date closed: 04-07-83
- Ford Motor Company and United Plant Guard Workers, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  Work Assignment: Car Check Out; Compulsory Overtime. Date closed: 09-29-82
- Mahoning County (Ohio) Board of Mental Retardation & Developmental Disabilities and Mahoning County Ed. Assn., 1983 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  Fringe Benefits: Parental Leave of Absence; Conflict between Labor Agreement and Administrative Rule, External Laws of Ohio. Date closed: 12-06-83
- Western Renaissance Corp. & Hotel, Motel Restaurant etc., 1982 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Discipline: Fighting. Date closed: 12-23-82
- Square D Company and IBEW, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Discipline: Leaving Work Early. Date closed: 11-22-83
- Standard Automotive & UAW, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  Seniority: Temporary Transfers During Reduction in Force.. Date closed: 11-28-83
- USWA International Union and Local Union No. 3657, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Seniority: Job Placement on Dissolution of District 26. Date closed: 08-09-83
- Waterford Township and Water-ford Professional Fire Fighters Association, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Wages: Overtime Premium; "Tour of Duty".. Date closed: 08-04- 82
- General Telephone Company and IBEW, Local 1106, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Seniority and Ability; Bumping in Force Reduction. Date closed: 1-30-84
- Indian Trails, Inc. and ATU, Local 130 3, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Discipline; Negligent Operation of Coach; False Reports. Date closed: 3-8-84
- Malincrodt, Inc. and UAW Local 1887, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Discharge: Quitting Early; Repeated Violations; Corrective Discipline.. Date closed: 2-2-84
- City of Menominee and IBT Local 328, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Seniority: Loss of: Municipal Residency Policy. Date closed: 10-10-84
- The Quad City Garage and ATU, Local 313, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  New Contract Terms. Date closed: 8-8-84
- Smith Meter Div. (Moorco Inc.), 1984 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  Arbitration: Multiple Grievances. Date closed:; 10-31-84
- Chattanooga Transportation Authority and ATU, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  Discharge: Cutting Trips; Interference with Operations; Unbecoir ing Conduct.. Date closed: i-
- Copaz Packing Corporation & United Food and Commercial Workers Union, Local 7A, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  Remedy for Wrongful Discharge. Date closed: 4-2-84
- Smurfit Graphic Arts and Graphic Arts Intl. Local 508, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  Seniority: Promotions. Date closed: 4-23-85
- Fort Wayne Comm. Schools and Ft. Wayne Ed. Association, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  Management's Rights; Obligation to Create and Staff Jobs; New Job, Computer Operator. Date closed: 10-30-84
- Escanaba Paper Company and United Paperworkers Intl., 1984 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  Working Conditions: Filling Vacancies; Crew Size. Date closed: 3-28-84
- Newberg, Construction Company and IBEW, Local 269, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  Management Rights; Hiring; Discrimination. Date closed: 4-5-84
- Witco Chemical Corporation and United Rubber etc. Workers, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  Overtime: Equalization of: Cross Assignments.. Date closed: 7-2-84
- The Westin Hotel and Hotel, Motel etc. Union Local 24 ', 1984 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  Discipline: Discourtesy to Hotel Guests.. Date closed: 1-23-84
- The City of Wyoming and Wyoming City Employees Union, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  Overtime Distribution. Date closed: 4-16-84
- The D. L. Auld Company and IBT, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Discipline: Discharge for Fighting; Equal Penalties. Date closed: 07-02-85
- Eberhard Foods, Inc & IBT, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  Recognition: Contracting Out; Distribution of Foodstuffs by Truck. Date closed: 03-28-85
- Findlay Board of Education & Findlay Education Assn., 1985 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  Seniority: Reduction in Force Limited Contract Teachers. Date closed: ;07- 18-85
- General Telephone Company of Indiana, Inc. & IBEW, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  Discipline: Attendance Irregularities; Absence without Fault.. Date closed: 07- 10-85
- Montgomery Ward & Company and IBT, Local 243, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  Recognition: Use of Part-time Employees. Date closed: 03-07-85
- Motor Wheel Corporation & United Rubber etc. Workers, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  Discipline: Absenteeism.. Date closed: 06-26-85
- Dietrich Industries, Inc. & IAMAW Local 2484, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  Discipline: Discharge for Just Cause; Poor Workmanship & Insubordination.. Date closed: 12-04-80
- Green River Steel Company and USWA Local 4 9 59, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  Seniority-Move Ups-Waivers. Date closed: 08-08-80
- Hastings Manufacturing Co. and UAW Local 138, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  Fringe Benefits: Damaged Shoes in Foundry Work.. Date closed: 12-09-80
- Hastings Manufacturing Co. and UAW Local 138, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  Recognition: Supervisors Performing Bargaining Unit Work.. Date closed: 12-09-80
- Malincrodt Inc. & UAW Local 1887, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  Discipline: Leaving Plant Without Permission or Notice; Falsification of Time Records. Date closed: 08-18-80
- Means Stamping Company & UAW Local 455, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  Discharge: Repeated Misconduct Corrective Discipline.. Date closed: t; 04-29- 80
- Midwest Machinery Movers, Inc. & IBT, Local 337, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  Discharge: Major Chargeable Accident.. Date closed: 03-10-80
- Midwest Machinery Movers Inc. and Local 337, IBT, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  Discipline: Refusal to Work Overtime.. Date closed: 03-12-80
- Midwest Machinery Movers Inc. and Local 337, IBT, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  Work Assignments: Casual Employes Displacing Seniority Employes: Overtime vs Straight Time.. Date closed: 03-12-80
- Midwest Machinery Movers Inc. Local 337, IBT, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  Seniority: RQ call from Layoff; Casual Employment.. Date closed: 03-10-80
- Olofsson Corporation and UAW Local 724, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  Discharge: Fraud; Leaving Plant without Permission.. Date closed: 10-28-80
- Sheet Metal Workers Local 533 and Office & Professional Workers Union No. 10, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  Disloyalty: Keeping Time Record on Supervisor.. Date closed: 08-28-80
- Addison Products Company 1 Local 1141, UAW, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  Benefits: Insurance; Changes in Coverage.. Date closed: 10-22-80
- Ames Company and USWA Local 8350, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  Wages: Overtime Pay for Non-Normal Hours Worked.. Date closed: 10-02-80
- Broad Corporation and Shopmen's Local No. 508, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  Seniority: Loss of: Leave of Absence.. Date closed: 05-27-80
- Brown Fintube Company and UAW, Local 99 6, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  Benefits: Major Medical for Retirees.. Date closed: 10-21-80
- Caramagno Foods Company and Teamsters Local No. 337, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  Wages: Cost of Living Allowance; Formula Changes.. Date closed: 07-02-80
- Celotex Corporation and United Paper Workers Int'l. Union, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  AAA Case No. 52 30 0040 78. Date closed: 02-26-80
- Cleveland Electric Illuminating Company and Utility Workers of America Local 270, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  AAA Case No. 53 30 0284 79 Seniority: Choice of Function.. Date closed: 02-18-80
- Dearborn Inn & United Catering, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  Discharge: Repeated Violations.. Date closed: 01-07-80
- Diamond International & UPIU Local 1973, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  Discipline: Unauthorized Work Stoppage; Extent of Penalty.. Date closed: 05-19-80